[{"id": 2118, "question": "Although the weathermen's forecasts for a month ahead are only little better than guesswork, they are now making long-term forecasts into the next century with growing confidence. For the main trend (, ) in the world's climate in the coming years will, scientists say, be a predictable result of man's activities. At the start of the industrial revolution nearly two centuries ago, man set off a big experiment in planetary engineering. Unaware of what he was doing, he spared no thought for the consequences .Today the possible outcome is alarmingly clear, but the experiment is unstoppable. Within the lifetimes of many of us, the Earth may become warmer than it has been for a thousand years. By the middle of this century it may be warmer than it has been since before the last Ice Age. A warmer ...\n\nQ: Scientists are fairly sure that, by the year 2050,   _  .", "options": ["the sea-level will have risen obviously", "there will have been a third World War", "most countries will have been flooded", "the polar ice-caps will have melt completely"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 339, "question": "John Blanchard stood up from the bench, straightened his Army uniform, and studied the crowd of people making their way through Grand Central Station. He looked for the girl whose heart he knew, but whose face he didn't, the girl with the rose. His interest in her had begun thirteen months before in a Florida library. Taking a book off the shelf he found himself intrigued, not with the words of the book, but with the notes penciled in the margin. The soft handwriting reflected a thoughtful soul and insightful mind. In the front of the book, he discovered the previous owner's name, Miss Hollis Maynell. With time and effort he located her address. She lived in New York City. He wrote her a letter introducing himself and inviting her to correspond. The next day he was shipped overseas for ser...\n\nQ: Hollis refused to send Blanchard a photo because  _  .", "options": ["she was only a middle - aged woman", "she wasn't confident about her appearance", "she thought true love is beyond appearance", "she had never taken any photo before they knew"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 470, "question": "VINCOUVER (Reuters)----South Korea' s Kirn Yuna can finally relax and does fiot need to think about the future after she won the gold medal in the women' s figure skating on Thursday. The 19-year-old was the overwhelming favorite to finish top of the podium but said the pressure going into the event was large. \"I feel now as if a huge burden has been lifted, \" the Games' highest-earning female athlete-she makes an estimated $8 million a year --said after her near-perfect program where she nailed all of her 11 jumps. \"I will enjoy this moment and think about things later.I was just thrilled on the podium and I feel so relieved.I had been running toward this dream of the Olympics and was so happy to be here, \" she said. \"Since I have achieved the most important goal in my life.I am going to ...\n\nQ: Kim Yuna felt relaxed because  _  .", "options": ["the competition was over", "her dream finally came true", "she won a large amount of money", "she became well-known overnight"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2749, "question": "Science Daily (Apr. 27, 2008)-- Dutch ecologist Roxina Soler and her colleagues have discovered that subterranean and aboveground herbivorous insects can communicate with each other by using plants as telephones. Subterranean insects issue chemical warning signals through the leaves of the plant. This way, aboveground insects are warned that the plant is already \"occupied\". Aboveground, leaf-eating insects prefer plants that have not yet been occupied by subterranean root-eating insects. Subterranean insects send out chemical signals through the leaves of the plant, which warn the aboveground insects about their presence. This messaging makes it possible for spatially-separated insects to avoid each other, so that they do not compete for, the same plant. In recent years it has been discove...\n\nQ: How do subterranean and aboveground insects communicate with each other?", "options": ["By sending signals through the leaves.", "By giving off particular smells.", "By making soft and beautiful sounds.", "By the signals sent by parasitic wasps."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2632, "question": "Beijing (Xinhua) -- In 2010, some 108,000 people returned to the Chinese mainland from abroad, a number that had risen 56.2 percent from the previous year, according to statistics recently published by the Ministry of Education. \"For Chinese employers, a 70 percent willingness to hire overseas workers, although that is still lower than the average rate of 76 percent for Asia, is quite a high figure when compared with the past,\" said Emma, regional director of Hays in Hong Kong and the mainland, who was in charge of the survey . Company executives , she said, have recently come to prefer hiring Chinese natives who have returned home after studying or working elsewhere.Expatriates have fallen to a second choice, she said. In the past, expatriates and returned Chinese have earned three to fou...\n\nQ: Why are overseas job candidates gradually losing their advantage?", "options": ["Because more and more overseas candidates are returning home.", "Because their qualifications are decreasing little by little.", "Because the job markets don't need overseas workers any more.", "Because China is raising workers' salaries on a large scale."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 854, "question": "The South Pole is a particular place on the earth.When people stand at the top of it looking around,they will find all directions face to north.No matter how they make their first step in which direction,they will always walk towards the north.That's to say,only north and south exist there,neither east nor west exists. At the top of the South Pole,any clock or watch keeps good time because all meridians join there.All kinds of local time are completely suitable there.It is even difficult to distinguish New Year's Eve from New Year's Day. The explorers and scientists from different countries always fix the time according to their own.Therefore the time by their watches was different when the people with different nationality gathered there. The Winter Solstice is an important festival at th...\n\nQ: At the top of the South Pole,your watch will   _  .", "options": ["keep good time", "be five minutes fast", "stop", "be ten minutes slow"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2899, "question": "Until last spring, Nia Parker and the other kids in her neighborhood went to school on Bus 59.But as fuel prices rose, the school district needed to find a way to cut its transportation costs.So the school's busing company redrew its route map, canceling Nia's bus.Now Nia and her neighbors travel the half mile to school via a \"walking school bus\"--a group of kids, supervised by an adult or two, who make the walk together. Many parents are delighted to see their kids walking to school, partly because many did so themselves.According to a 1979 survey, nearly half of school kids walked or biked to school, compared with only 16 percent in 2011.Modern parents have been unwilling to let kids walk to school for fear of traffic, crime or simple bullying, but with organized adult supervision, those...\n\nQ: To save money, some schools choose to   _  .", "options": ["shorten the school week", "take the shortest routes", "stop using school buses", "use fuel-efficient buses"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2861, "question": "The sunflower plant bears bright yellow flowers that always face the sun, hence the name. However, the plant is grown not only for its beautiful flowers, but also for its oil that has a host of health benefits. Sunflower oil prevents diseases, lowers cholesterol levels, keeps the heart healthy, and even prevents certain forms of cancer. Sunflower oil is a kind of \"magic oil\" when it comes to skin care, as it makes your skin soft and smooth, and prevents signs of aging. So, let us know more about its effects on your skin. 1. It Acts as an Effective Emollient . Sunflower oil is an effective emollient, which means that it helps the skin retain moisture. Thus, people with dry skin can benefit immensely from the regular use of the oil. Also, it is mild, and provides relief from irritation and i...\n\nQ: Sunflower oil can be good for the following EXCEPT   _  .", "options": ["reducing cholesterol levels", "preventing heart diseases", "making skin smooth and impressive", "curing some kinds of cancers"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 885, "question": "There's a widespread perception in the United States that a university degree is the key to success. But a growing number of educators now say there are other possibilities, especially for students who might not succeed at university level. This is not a traditional classroom. At the apprentice program run by the Plumbers and Steamfitters Union in the state of Maryland, Travis Strawderman and other students make money while they learn. \"I \\t's completely changed my life around,\" he said. \"I've been able to pay off all my debts. I can say I'm actually responsible enough to have my own family.\" Strawderman's five-year program teaches him technical skills free of charge. He says he considered university, but it didn't interest him. Economics Professor Robert Lerman says Strawderman is not alo...\n\nQ: What can we infer from the passage?", "options": ["Robert and Chad have different opinions.", "Professor Lerman teaches Travis technical skills.", "Travis will have a high paying and stable career.", "Travis liked high school and studied well"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2581, "question": "During a state of deep relaxation, several physiological changes take place in the body: the body's oxygen consumption is reduced; the heart beat decreases; muscle tension and sweating ease, and there is decreased sympathetic nervous system activity.This restful state not only allows the body to repair and restore itself, but it has a calming effect on the consciousness. How to achieve this state of relaxation, however, is a matter of opinion, and in some medical circles, a matter of controversy.A recent report by Dr.David Holmes of the University of Kansas in the journal \"American psychologist\" said that simply sitting in an armchair has just as many beneficial characteristics for the body as meditation does.Researchers of other relaxation techniques disagree.These experts believe that mo...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following statements is NOT true when a person is in a state of deep relaxation?", "options": ["The body takes in less oxygen.", "The heart beats less frequently.", "Muscles become tense and the body sweats easily.", "The consciousness becomes more or less calmed."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 739, "question": "How to protect children Web fans from unsuitable material on-line while encouraging them to use the Internet has long been discussed in the US. For some parents, the Internet can seem like a jungle, filled with danger for their children. But jungles contain wonders as well as danger. With good guides, some education, and a few precautions( ), the wilds of the Internet can be safely navigated. \"Kids have to be on-line. If we tell our kids they can't be allowed to surf the Internet, we're cutting them off from their future,\" said an expert. Most kids have started to use search engines. Many of them are great for finding tons of interesting Internet sites, and they can also locate places where you might not want your kids to go. There are search engines designed just for kids. A certain softw...\n\nQ: According to the passage, we can infer that   _  .", "options": ["softwares that are fit for children who want programming", "the Internet contains a lot of harmful sites", "the Internet will be protected by law", "a child who is on-line is in danger"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 622, "question": "Is there anything more important than health?I don't think so.You can't be good at your studies or work when you are ill. If you have a headache,or a bad cough,if you run a high temperature and have a bad cold,I think you should go to the doctor. The doctor will examine your throat,feel your pulse,take your temperature,sound your heart and lungs.After that he will advise some treatment,or some medicine.The only thing you have to do is to follow his advice. Speaking of doctor's advice,I can't help telling you a funny story. An old man came to see the doctor.The man was very ill.He told the doctor about his weakness,memory loss and serious problems with his heart and lungs.The doctor examined him and said there was no medicine for his disease. He told his patient to go to a quiet place for a...\n\nQ: The doctor usually tells his patient what to do   _  .", "options": ["without examining the patient", "after he has examined the patient", "if the patient doesn't take medicine", "unless the patient feels pain"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3254, "question": "Teachers and textbooks _ -- your future could be under threat from a quickly developing and very smart technology. University of California researchers led by Jacob White hill recently programmed teaching robots to react to facial expression. Whitehill's achievement marked a major step forward in the way people could one day learn by establishing facial expression recognition in robot teachers. The teaching robots or, Intelligent Tutoring Systems (ITS) are computer systems that provide personalized instruction and feedback to students without human intervention. The facial expression recognition allows a computer to react according to expressions a user makes. He said that the system was an important development in improving learning systems. \"Classical ITS typically have a somewhat rigid ...\n\nQ: Compared with classical ITS, developed ITS can", "options": ["ask and answer questions in turns", "provide feedback to students in less time", "somewhat interact with the students", "make different facial expressions"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2422, "question": "Millions of girls grow up with the hope of becoming a famous singer. Some even win local talent competitions as children, but only a few such early successes and dreams turn into reality. Jessica Andrews is one of the few whose dreams have come true. Andrews, first taste of success came at the age of 10. She won a talent competition in her home town of Huntingdon, Tennessee, singing I Will Always Love You, originally sung by Whitney Houston. Houston's version of the song appeared on The Bodyguard sound track, which happened to be the first album Andrews ever bought. Within two years, talk of Andrews had spread to Nashville and caught the attention of producer Byron Gallimore, whose credits include work with Tim McGraw, Faith Hill, and Jo Dee Messina. With Gallimore signed on to produce, An...\n\nQ: According to the passage, who mostly helped Andrews to achieve success ?", "options": ["Tim McGraw", "Whitney Houston", "Faith Hill", "Byron Gallimore"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1858, "question": "MONTAGNE: In the summer of 2011, the world first heard of a small island in Norway under the most terrible of circumstances. Utoya Island was a youth camp run by Norway's Labor Party. One day in July, a heavily armed, right-wing extremist stepped onto the island and began shooting at random. Sixty-nine people died, over 100 were wounded; almost all, young people. This month, artist Jonas Dahlberg was appointed to create a memorial. He described to us the experience he imagines for those who come to the island. DAHLBERG: You start your walk through a forest of evergreens on a wooden pathway. After a while, this pathway starts to go down into the landscape. MONTAGNE: Down into the landscape, and into a short tunnel. When you come out, you are unable to go any farther. You can't get to the ti...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is TRUE?", "options": ["Utoya Island was the only bloody shooting spot planned by the killer.", "Utoya Island used to be a youth camp site and now has been reduced to total silence.", "Dahlberg and his brother witnessed the shooting on Utoya Island.", "Visitors to Utoya Island can touch the names of the victims carved on the polished stone."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2964, "question": "Advertisers tend to think big and perhaps this is why they're always getting criticism. Their critics seem to resent(...) them because they have a gift for self-promotion and because they have so much money to throw around. 'It's unjust,' they say, 'that this entirely unproductive industry (if we can call it that) should absorb millions of pounds each year. It only goes to show how much profit the big companies are making. Why don't they stop advertising and reduce the price of their goods? After all, it's the consumer who pays...' The poor old consumer! He'd have to pay a great deal more if advertising didn't create mass markets for products. It is precisely because of the heavy advertising that consumer goods are so cheap. But we get the wrong idea if we think the only purpose of adverti...\n\nQ: Why do the critics criticize advertisers?", "options": ["Because advertisers often brag .", "Because critics think advertisement is a \"waste of money\".", "Because customers are encouraged to buy more than necessary.", "Because customers pay more."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 792, "question": "In my living room, there is a plaque that advises me to \"Bloom where you are planted.\" It reminds me of Dorothy. I got to know Dorothy in the early 1980s, when I was teaching Early Childhood Development through a program with Union College in Barbourville, Kentucky. The job responsibilities requested occasional visits to the classroom of each teacher in the program. Dorothy stands out in my memory as one who \"bloomed\" in her remote area. Dorothy taught in a school In Harlan County, Kentucky, Appalachian Mountain area. To get to her school from the town of Harlan, I followed a road winding around the mountain. In the eight-mile journey, I crossed the same railroad track five times, giving the possibility of getting caught by the same train five times. Rather than feeling excited by this dri...\n\nQ: Upon arriving at the classroom, the author was cheered up by   _  .", "options": ["a warm welcome", "the sight of poke greens", "Dorothy's latest projects", "a big dinner made for her"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3279, "question": "Boxing was long viewed sickly. Generally forbidden by law in earlier days, the fighting was usually done with bare fists, and matches often lasted forty or fifty rounds. In 1882 John L. Sullivan, a fighter of great power, won the world heavyweight championship from Paddy Ryan in a bare fisted battle marked by hitting, scratching, and biting without any rule. Five years later, while fighting Patsy Cardiff at Minneapolis, Sullivan broke his right arm in the third round, but he continued fighting to the sixth round and won. In 1889, Sullivan defeated Jade Kilrain with his bare fists in another championship fight, winning twenty thousand dollars and a diamond prize medal. His admirers talked then of running him for the next governor, but he traveled to Australia for a boxing tour instead, comi...\n\nQ: Boxing matches in the early days were   _  .", "options": ["short and bloody", "usually spare-time competitions", "governed by strict rules", "cruel"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 43, "question": "One of the traditions which is now a necessary part of Christmas is a that of Father Christmas, or Santa Claus. According to the modern legend, he is a magical figure who visits all the children of the world during the night before Christmas Day, leaving presents which they find the next morning. He flies through the night sky in a sledge pulled by reindeer, and enters houses by climbing down chimneys. This strange legend is based on the life of a man called Nicholas, but in fact we know very little about him. Historians think he was a Christian bishop in Turkey in about 285--350 A.D. One of the stories about him is that he helped three poor girls. No one would marry them because they were so poor. To provide them with money for their weddings, Nicholas secretly dropped some gold coins dow...\n\nQ: Why does the writer mention the story about St Nicholas helping three poor girls?", "options": ["It shows us that historians know very little about him.", "This story explains why parents give secret presents to children.", "It supports the writer's main point that Father Christmas is based on an untrue story.", "This story explains why we celebrate Christmas in December."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 990, "question": "Traditionally, women have fallen behind men in adoption of Internet technologies, but a study released yesterday by the Pew Internet & American Life Project found that women under age 65 now get ahead of men in Internet usage, though only by a few percentage points. But the survey also noted that the _ between women and men on the Web is even greater among the 18-to-29 age group and African Americans. The report, \"How Women and Men Use the Internet\", examined use by both sexes, looking at what men and women are doing online as well as their rate of adopting new Web-based technologies. The report found that 86 percent of women aged 18 to 29 were online, compared with 80 percent of men in the same age group. Among African Americans, 60 percent of women are online, compared with 50 percent of...\n\nQ: What does the passage mainly tell us?", "options": ["Women are catching up in the use of the Internet.", "Men and women use the Internet for different purposes.", "How people use the Internet in different age groups", "Why women fall behind in the adoption of Internet technologies."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1193, "question": "Harvard researchers have created a tough, low-cost, biodegradable material inspired by insects' hard outer shells. The material's inventors say it has a number of possible uses and someday could provide a more environmentally friendly alternative to plastic. The material, made from shrimp (') shells and proteins produced from silk, is called \"shrilk.\" It is thin, clear, flexible and strong. A major benefit of the material is its biodegradability. Plastic's toughness and flexibility represented a revolution in materials science during the 1950s and '60s. Decades later, however, plastic's very durability is raising questions about how appropriate it is for one-time products such as plastic bags, or short-lived consumer goods, used in the home for a few years and then cast into a landfill whe...\n\nQ: What has become a concern about plastic?", "options": ["Using it properly.", "Producing it cheaply.", "Developing its properties quickly.", "Evaluating its contributions fairly."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 393, "question": "There's a man in the habit of hitting me on the head with an umbrella.At first I couldn't stand it;now I'm used to it. I don't know his name.I know he's average in appearance,wears a gray suit.and has a common face one hot morning,when 1 was sitting off a tree-shaded bench in Palermo Park,reading the paper,suddenly I felt something touch my head.It was the very same man who now,as I'm writing.keeps striking me with an umbrella. On that occasion I turned around filled with anger.He just kept on hitting me.I asked him if he was crazy.He didn't even seem to hear me.Thell I threatened to call a policeman.Calmly.cool as a cucumber,he stuck with his task.After a few moments of hesitation,and seeing that he was not about to change his attitude,I stood up and hit him on the nose.The man fell down....\n\nQ: The author would most probably agree that he man was_.", "options": ["deaf", "blind", "dead", "mad"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2327, "question": "Starting college can be a difficult experience. You have to deal with new responsibilities, growing independence, a challenging course load, and of course, the social scene. When a roommate is thrown into the mix, it may feel like you're struggling with all that stuff while living in a small box with a stranger. But having a roommate doesn't need to be one more thing to worry about. When students go into their living situations with realistic expectations and a willingness to _ , things can work out just fine. When you first meet your roommate, chances are that you'll be on your best behavior. You want to get along since this is the person who's going to be sharing your living space for the next year. But try to think ahead to potential worst cases, too. For example, imagine it's 2 am and ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE according to this passage?", "options": ["It is really a worrying thing to have a roommate.", "It is difficult to get along well with your roommate.", "It is your duty to help your roommate in the daily life.", "It is very important for you and your roommate to understand each other."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1553, "question": "City Varieties The Headrow, Leeds. Tel. 430808 Oct 10-11 only A Night at the Varieties.All the fun of an old music hall with Barry Cryer, Duggle Brown, 6 dancers, Mystina, Jon Barker, Anne Dural and the Tony Harrison Trio. Laugh again at the old jokes and listen to your favourite songs. Performances: 8 pm nightly. Admission: L5; under 16 or over 60: L4. York Theatre Royal prefix = st1 /St Leonard's Place, York. Tel. 223568 Sept 23- Oct 17 Groping for Words-- a comedy by Sue Townsend. Best known for her Adrian Mole Diaries, Townsend now writes about an evening class, which two men and a woman attend. A gentle comedy. Admission: First night, Mon: L2; Tues- Fri: L3.25 - 5.50; Sat: L3.50 - 5.75. Halifax Playhouse King's Cross Street, Halifax. Tel. 365998 Oct 10-17 On Golden Pondby Ernest Thomp...\n\nQ: We may learn from the text that Sue Townsend is  _  .", "options": ["a writer", "an actress", "a musician", "a director"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2925, "question": "Steps Shoes Salon Steps Shoes Salon, 4518 S.Cottage Grove, knows our \"economy is weathering a little storm\" They've discounted winter botts and shoes for their fellow shoes lovers.So step in and save! Hours: 11a.m.to 7 p.m.Monday through Friday; 11 a.m.to 6 p.m.Saturaday; Noon to 5 p.m.the first Sunday of this month (closeed other Sundays).Call 773-548 Jonathan Saunders for Target If you've ever watched a runway shoes and thought \"yeah, that dress would be awesome if it wasn't $ 1,800\", you'll be very pleased to know that British designer Jonathan Saunders has decided to use his powers for good and offer fashion - forward clothing.His collection was inspired by the works of Gustav Klimt, Jackson Pollack and Rothko.The clothing ranges from $ 14.99 to $ 29.99 and is only available until Nove...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of the first part?", "options": ["The world is being hit by an economic downturn", "Steps Shoe Salon is providing weather forecast for us.", "A snowstorm has interrupted the traffic in Cottage Grove.", "Steps Shoe Salon marks down winter shoes and boots."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 981, "question": "NEW DELHI, India (AP)--India is fast becoming a top destination for tourists thanks to a forceful campaign to push the country's Himalayan spas and beaches, officials say. Tourism officials have been crisscrossing the globe as part of the government's \"Incredible India\" campaign launched in 2003. And the results are beginning to show. Tourists traveling to prefix = st1 /Indiahave jumped by nearly 26 percent from last year and the number is expected to cross 3 million this year, said Amitabh Kant, chairman of the India Tourism Development Corp. \"Foreign exchange earnings, too, have shown a nearly 40 percent rise this year,\" Kant told The Associated Press. India's earnings from tourism were $4.3 billion between January and November 2004, compared to $3.1 billion for the same period of 2003. ...\n\nQ: It can be learned that   _  .", "options": ["Kant is satisfied with the trend of tourism", "Kant worries about the future of India's tourism", "Choudhury doesn't think the situations of tourism will improve", "Choudhury thinks Indiashould make full preparations for the crisis of tourists"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1048, "question": "Cyberspace, the connections between computers in different places, considered as a real place where information, messages and pictures exist, mirrors the real world in many ways. People ask for information, play games, and share hobbies. Others buy and sell products. Still others look for friendship, or even love. Unlike the real world, however, your knowledge about a person is limited to words on a computer screen. Identity and appearance mean very little in cyberspace. Rather, a person's thoughts--or at least the thoughts they type--are what really count. So even the shyest person can become a chat room star. Usually, this \"faceless\" communication doesn't create problems. Identity doesn't really matter when you're in a chat room discussing politics or hobbies. In fact, this emphasis(,) o...\n\nQ: People who are against online love think   _  .", "options": ["what is said online is under control of the Internet", "it is hard to protect the other's identity", "the faceless communication is exciting", "one may not show the real self in cyberspace"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1390, "question": "In the market of luxury brands, Chinese consumers are only second to the Japanese in the world. Across the globe it's clear that the young generation are increasingly relying on expensive brands for their self-image. Personally I am a fashion-lover, at least in spirit. I love to look at clothes and shoes. But I don't understand why people spend large amounts of money on designer labels. Certainly, young people, whether in China or elsewhere, should be building their self-confidence in other ways. When a young woman shows off a handbag worth two months' salary, that's a scary thing. What are the psychological factors forcing young people to take on debt for designer items? The desire to say, \"Hey, look at me. I'm wealthy. I have social status.\" Scientists have found the acquisition of luxur...\n\nQ: This passage is written here in order to   _  .", "options": ["encourage young people to travel", "persuade young people to seek experience happiness", "report the result of a series of researches", "advise young people to save money"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1101, "question": "Hilton English Language Center Information for New Students CLASS TIME: 8:30a.m.--10:00a.m., 10:30a.m.--12:00a.m., 1:30p.m.--3:00p.m.. The Language Center is open Monday to Friday. Each class has one afternoon free per week. On the first day, go to the lecture hall to check your timetable. SELF-ACCESS: The language laboratory (Room 1110) is open Monday to Friday from 3:15p.m. to 5:00p.m. for all full-time students. You can learn how to use computers for language games or word-processing . There are tapes for students to borrow to practice their English. Go in and ask the teacher to show you. If you plan to take public examinations, there are dictation and listening comprehension tapes for you to practice with. There are cloze exercises on the computers. Ask your class teacher for a list of...\n\nQ: The timetable can be seen in   _  .", "options": ["the lecture hall", "Room 3520", "the classroom", "Room 1110"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1501, "question": "First Lady Michelle Obama is a big fan of volunteering. Volunteering means working for free to help someone else. Mrs. Obama says volunteering is very important. \"It should be part of everyone's life, \" she says. Many teens agree. They say that helping others feels great and makes a difference. These days, more teens volunteer than work for pay. Teens clean up parks, walk dogs at animal shelters , visit the elderly and more. Some cities ---- including Seatle, Chicago, and Washingtong,D.C. ----require high school students to volunteer. Students must volunteer in order to graduate. The student volunteers learn new skills and help theircommunities . Many parents _ the idea ---- they say volunteering helps teens build job skills. But most teens don't want to be forced to volunteer. They say th...\n\nQ: Which question does the text mainly discuss?", "options": ["Is volunteering good for students?", "What is the best time to volunteer?", "Should students be required to volunteer?", "Which volunteer jobs should students do?"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2142, "question": "Skin - diving is a new sport today. This sport takes you into a wonderful new world. It is like a visit to the moon. When you are under water, it is easy for you to climb big rocks because you are no longer heavy .Here, under water, everything is blue and green. During the day, there is plenty of light. When fish swim nearby, you can catch them with your hands.When you have tanks of air on your back, you can stay in deep water for a long time. But you must be careful when you dive in deep water. To catch fish is one of the most interesting parts of this sport. Besides, there are more uses for skin - diving. You can clean ships without taking them out of water. You can get many things from the deep sea. Now you see that skin -diving is both useful and interesting....\n\nQ: In deep water  _  .", "options": ["there is plenty of light", "there is no light at all", "you can find a lot of blue fish", "everything looks blue and green"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1454, "question": "Read the advertisements carefully.Then answer the questions that follow. INTERESTED IN CHILDCARE? Qualified person or preschool teacher needed for busy childcare center, south of the river.Full-time work guaranteed.Immediate start necessary.The candidate must be able to work as a co-operative team member.Phone 6345 2345 for an interview and fax resume to 6345 2345. WE NEED OFFICE CLEANERS! Three people are required for professional cleaning in the CBD area.Working hours from 5:00 pm on Mondays, Wednesdays & Fridays.Approximately five hours per shift.A good record is necessary.Experience preferred.Phone 6345 7843 now. WANT TO WORK AS A DENTAL NURSE? This is an exciting opportunity for a qualified dental nurse with a confident and cheerful personality to work in the School Dental Health Sche...\n\nQ: The position of a(n)  _  is a part-time job.", "options": ["florist", "artist", "preschool teacher", "dental nurse"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 100, "question": "I've done many things that would make any parent proud. I've taken part in sports, community work and school events, but I am most proud to be a good big brother. I have to watch over four sisters and a brother, plus myself. That's quitea task, but one I feel I have gotten good at. My brother needs more attention than most siblings. When he was nine, he was hit by a pick-up truck on the way to the bus stop and lost use of the lower two-thirds of his body. He's been in a wheelchair for six years. My brother does many things, but sometimes he tries to do things he used to do but can't now. I' m always there with words of encouragement. I now watch my brother struggle to do as many things as he can within and beyond his limits. Should he fall, I will be the person to pick him up. I also watch...\n\nQ: We can learn from the text that a big brother   _  .", "options": ["sometimes takes more responsibilities", "must put up with the incredible hardship", "can be asked for help whenever needed", "is the most important guy in a big family"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 796, "question": "When I opened my e-mail the other day, a pretty woman named Rachel appeared on my computer screen. She greeted me by name and started talking with great enthusiasm . Every now and then she stopped to smile at me or blow a kiss. She was reading to me an e-mail from my brother, and a lot of it was about the trouble he had getting the phone company to give him a high-speed Internet connection. It was pretty cool. Rachel was there thanks to a new technology called Facemail. An ace man lets you send an e-mail that gets ready to the recipient by an attractive male or female from or by a clown . The software, which is free, can be downloaded at www.facemail.com. Facemail faces are lifelike, and they simulate emotions based on emotions-for example, that you put in your text. Type in; -x, and Rache...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that Facemail_.", "options": ["can destroy your e-mail if not properly used", "can be downloaded free of charge s", "will take the place of the e-mail system", "is likely to be used in other aspects of our daily life"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 693, "question": "Jenny went to visit her friends in New York last weekend.Her friends met her at the airport on Friday afternoon and drove her to the hotel.They had dinner at a Chinese restaurant and went to see a film after that. Jenny and her friends set out early on Saturday morning for a farm and stayed there until Sunday morning.During their stay, they went fishing and swimming in the small river on the farm.They played football in the field and enjoyed a big meal around a camp fire , singing and dancing till late into the night. Nobody could get up early on Sunday morning.So when they got back to New York City, it was about three o'clock in the afternoon.They drove right to the airport because Jenny didn't want to miss her plane back home.Jenny only stayed in New York for two nights but she had a gre...\n\nQ: Jenny went to New York  _  .", "options": ["to do some shopping", "to see her friends", "to spend her summer holiday", "to find a job"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3105, "question": "When I was 18, I had a motorbike accident that put me in a coma for three months. The doctors said there was little chance of my coming out of it, but my identical twin, Marcus, didn't believe them and carried on talking to me. My first words when I came to myself were, \"Hello, Marcus. \"Even though I had no memory of my own name, or that the woman crying at my bedside was my mother, I knew Marcus immediately; it was like a genetic memory. just felt close to him. As weeks went by, I still could remember nothing before the accident. Marcus was the only person I could relate to. I had to relearn everything, and Marcus helped me. Because of my twin I wasn't scared of having lost my memory; I believed everything he said. He became my memory, telling me about my school, friends, previous girlfri...\n\nQ: How did the author feel when he first got his memories back?", "options": ["Angry.", "Excited", "Guilty.", "Lonely."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2371, "question": "Star Wars Millennium Falcon This is a gift that, if we're being honest, many dads want to own for themselves. This huge ship is the greatest Star Wars toy. It lights up and makes some noises. Every boy from 3 to 53 will absolutely like it, if they can find room for it. I dare say even a few grandfathers might go for it. Biscuit--the Loving Pup You may clearly know that a pet can be a great thing to a child's development but you probably don't think that you can take care of a dog properly. The robot dog Biscuit is less likely to the disorder of your house and except for a few dead batteries, won't leave any surprises on the floor. It will be a good playmate for your kids. JVC KD-10 Headphones It's increasingly common for kids to enjoy themselves on long journeys with a portable DVD player ...\n\nQ: The five things listed in the passage are    _    .", "options": ["presents for the whole family", "gifts mainly for children", "craft tools for children", "the latest high-tech products"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 304, "question": "Beginning college is exciting: new ideas to explore, new challenges to be met and many decisions to be made; your future begins here. However, you will find college life is different from your previous school environment. Many of us can be easily overwhelmed by the details of running a well-balanced life. While some of us may have the know-how, I guess there are more of us who can benefit from learning about the experiences of others who have walked the college halls before you. The following you may find of use about life on campus: *Plan well. There are so many new things to do at a new college or university. Give yourself time to make new friends and became familiar with the campus, but don't forget why you are there. Give some time for social activities and manage your time wisely. *If...\n\nQ: According to the passage, college students   _  .", "options": ["needn't learn from those who went to college before them", "spend as much time as possible on social activities", "should know what they have fight for on campus", "are supposed to repeat or replace at least one course"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1350, "question": "A jobless man applied for the position of \"office boy\" at Microsoft. The HR manager interviewed him and then watched him cleaning the floor as a test. \"You are employed,\" he said. \"Give me your e-mail address and I'll send you the application to fill in, as well as date when you may start. \" The man replied, \"But I don't have a computer, neither an e-mail. \" \"I'm sorry,\" said the HR manager. \"If you don't have an e-mail, that means you do not exist. And who doesn't exist cannot have the job. \" The man left with no hope at all. He didn't know what to do, with only ten dollars in his pocket. He then decided to go to the supermarket and buy 10kg tomatoes. He then sold the tomatoes from door to door. In less than two hours, he succeeded to double his capital. He repeated the operation three ti...\n\nQ: Why can't the man have the job at Microsoft?", "options": ["Because he was lazy.", "Because he didn't pass the test.", "Because he didn't have an e-mail.", "Because he didn't have a computer."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1689, "question": "Long long ago, there was a man who was good at shooting arrows.He asked the king to declare him as the greatest archer of the country.The king was about to do so when an old servant of the king said,\"Wait,sir.I know an old man who lives in the forest.He is a much greater archer.Let this young man go to him and learn from him for at least three years.\" The man could not believe what the servant said,but he went and found the old man and he was! For three years he learned from him.Then one day,when he thought he had learned everything,the thought arose in him:\"If I kill this old man,then I will be the greatest archer.\" The old man had gone to cut wood and he was coming back carrying wood on his shoulder.The young man hid behind a tree,waiting to kill him.He shot an arrow.The old man took a s...\n\nQ: The young archer wanted to kill the old man because  _  .", "options": ["he could then become the greatest archer", "he had nothing more to learn from him", "the old man refused to teach him everything", "the king's old servant ordered him to do SO"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2496, "question": "Sir, The majority(=Most) of your readers must have been surprised and shocked to read a letter from Mr.R.Hogg,published in last Wednesday's Herald.Mr.Hogg seems to think that his own convenience and that of motorists in general are the only things that matter in our city. I would have supported Mr.Hogg if he had just made suggestions to improve the situation.No doubt his problems would be partly solved if the local government built a multi-storey car park in the city center,instead of encouraging motorists to use public transport.All the same,judging from the tone of Mr.Hogg's letter,I suspect that motorists who are so careless of pedestrians' safety that they would rather park their ears on the pavement than hold up the traffic would probably be too lazy to use a multi-storey car park if ...\n\nQ: In Mr.A.Walker's opinion,severer punishment should be given to  _  .", "options": ["all the careless motorists", "all the law breakers", "all who step out into the road", "all who do dangerous parking"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2029, "question": "Is your family interested in buying a dog? A dog can be a pleasant companion to your family, but if you choose the wrong kind of dog , you will have a lot of troubles. Families should sit down and discuss the possible problems before buying a dog. Even if the children in your family are the ones who want the dog, the parents are the ones who are really responsible for seeing that the animal is properly cared for. If you don't know much about dogs, it is a good idea to go to the library for books about different kinds of dogs, and books about how to train a young dog. In reading about the different breeds you should know that a dog described as very alert may be too active. When a book describes a dog as an excellent hunting dog, it probably means that the dog won't be happy living in a sma...\n\nQ: According to the passage, one can get information about different kinds of dogs  _  .", "options": ["by going to the library", "by asking someone who has enough experience about different kinds of dogs", "by buying a dog and training it", "by reading books about dogs"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2003, "question": "A new report says the number of foreign students at colleges and universities in the United States increased by three percent last year. This has been the first obvious increase since 2001. American schools last fall had 583,000 foreign students. The record is 586,000. That was set in 2002 after many years of gains. But after that the numbers fell. The terrorist attacks on September 11th, 2001 led to more visa requirements. Now stronger efforts are being made to get more foreign students to study in the United States. China remained in second place in front of South Korea but behind India, whichsent almost 84,000 students last fall. The number of Japanese fell sharply by nine percent, although it remained in fourth place. There were three percent drops from Indonesia and Kenya, the only Af...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that   _   .", "options": ["Kenya is the only African country that has students in the USA", "now foreign students are encouraged to study in the USA", "the number of students studying in America always increases", "the number of foreign students in the USA will keep increasing in the future"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1926, "question": "Are you hard-working? Do you like to meet people? If your answer is \"Yes\", then we have a job for you as a waiter. Call AL Hotel at 556779! (2) SUMMER JOB Do you like to talk with people? Do you like to write stories? If you want to work for our magazine as a reporter, please call Karen at 558366. (3) HELP WANTED Do you like babies? Can you look after one baby for two days? If you are sure to take food care of it, call us at 766588. $80 or more. Today! Hurry! (4)CLEANER WANTED Can you make a large house clean and tidy? If you hope to get the job paid at $20 once, call us this evening 18:00-20:00. Tel:633800...\n\nQ: The above job ads  are probably from a   _  .", "options": ["newspaper", "story book", "TV show", "radio program"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1596, "question": "Narasimha Das is on his way to feed 169,379 hungry children. Das is in charge of a kitchen in Vrindaban. The town is about a three-hour drive from India's capital, New Delhi. Das gets to work at 3:00 a.m. Thirty workers are already working to make tens of thousands of rounds of bread. It will be brought to 1,516 schools in and around Vrindaban. A Growing Problem Going to school is difficult for more than 13 million children in India. They must go to work instead, or go hungry. That's why India began the Mid-Day Meal Scheme, the largest school-lunch program in the world. A free lunch encourages children to come to school and gives them the energy they need for learning. The program began in the 1960s. The kitchen in Vrindaban is run by the Akshaya Patra Foundation. It is one of the lunch pr...\n\nQ: Which of the following about the Mid-Day Meal Scheme is NOT true?", "options": ["It is run by Narasimha Das.", "It has been carried out for about 50 years.", "It is to encourage children to go to school.", "It is the largest school-lunch program in the world."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 356, "question": "America's child movie star Shirley Temple Black died late Monday evening at the age of 85. Her fans in China are also deeply saddened. Temple is just one example of movie stars that China adored, and still adores. Here's our editor's pick of the top movie stars who have influenced China. 1. Sylvester Stallone Oh, Rambo! The first strong American man that China knew. His accented English, easily recognizable even for someone who doesn't speak English, and his eyes that never seemed to smile, makes him someone whom cannot be forgotten. He represented the strong American image, and even stirred a boxing and bodybuilding fever in China. 2.Charlie Chaplin (April 16, 1889 - December 25, 1977) In the 20th century, it is not too much to say that Einstein made the greatest contributions to science,...\n\nQ: According to the passage, who was most known for comedy in China?", "options": ["Sylvester Stallone", "Charlie Chaplin", "Shirley Temple", "Audrey Hepburn"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2282, "question": "Where can you find a nice place to relax on holiday for both you and your children? Well, I suggest you try the beautiful and green Isle of Wight (IOW). The Isle of Wight is one of the main tourist attractions. Here is some information on a few of the attractions on the IOW. Dinosaur Isle It is located in Sandown, a seaside town on the southeast coast. It's a large, lovely museum, both fun and educational. Here you can see a large fossil collection of all kinds of dinosaurs, as well as a gift shop. You can walk into the past and then the future, learning about the history and the development of the civilization of dinosaurs that lived 120 million years ago. Robin Hill Country Park The park is in the beautiful countryside, and is suitable for children's parties and games. It has five new ga...\n\nQ: It can be learned from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["those running the Wight Bus Museum work for free", "on Dinosaur Isle we can learn about all kinds of animals", "there are five new gardens on Dinosaur Isle", "the Wight Bus Museum can be visited free of charge"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1947, "question": "Artie Shaw was born in New York City in 1910. His name was Arthur Arshawsky. His parents were poor immigrants who had come to the United States from Eastern Europe. His family later moved to New Haven, Connecticut. At the age of fourteen, he began to play the saxophone and then the clarinet. From a very young age, Artie Shaw wanted to play his clarinet better than anyone. He wanted his sound and music to be perfect. He worked at this task much of his life. He began working as a professional musician when he was fifteen. He left home and began playing in bands across the United States. In 1928, young Artie Shaw traveled to Chicago, Illinois to hear the great trumpet player, Louis Armstrong. He immediately understood that Armstrong's great jazz sound was the beginning of something new and ex...\n\nQ: In his later years, Artie Shaw    _   .", "options": ["almost stopped playing music", "worked for a magazine as an professional writer", "he made many speeches about his life at colleges", "he received many awards and honors for his books"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 677, "question": "Ben and his wife Susan were on their way to have dinner with their friends. It was a dark,windy night, and they did not know the way very well. They drove through a town until they found what they thought was the road to Dorling,where their friends lived. But it soon became clear that they were not on the road to Dorling at all. The road that they were on was getting narrower,and there were no other cars on it. The wind was blowing harder with every minute that passed. They came to a small village .They drove past a church and then two houses without lights on. There was nobody about to tell them where they were,or where the road went. Just then,Ben saw a telephone box,twenty meters or so further on. While he walked back along the road to see if there was a name outside the church,Susan te...\n\nQ: From the passage we know   _  .", "options": ["Ben and his wife often went out for dinners", "Ben and his wife lived in the country", "both Ben and his wife were shortsighted", "Ben and his wife seldom went to Dorling"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2627, "question": "Men sometimes say: \"We are better and cleverer than women. Women never invented things. We do.\" It is true that men have invented a lot of useful things: the alphabet, machines, rockets, and guns, too. But scientists and archeologists now agree that women invented one very important thing. It had changed the history. They invented agriculture. Before the invention of agriculture men were hunter. They went out every day. Sometimes they killed animals-sometimes animals killed them. Life was difficult and dangerous. Women had to go out every day, too. They collected roots, fruit and grass. Then, one day, more than 10,000years ago a woman dropped some grass seeds. She dropped them near her home in the Middle East. They grew--and the first wheat was born. The idea grew, too. Women planted roots...\n\nQ: Before agriculture was invented, life was difficult and dangerous because   _  .", "options": ["sometimes animals killed men", "women had to go hunting with their husbands", "men had to fight against animals", "only men went out for food every day"], "answer": 0}]